<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>With Fear and Trembling on Pritam Chandra</title>
    <link>https://pritamchandra.github.io/categories/with-fear-and-trembling/</link>
    <description>Recent content in With Fear and Trembling on Pritam Chandra</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://pritamchandra.github.io/categories/with-fear-and-trembling/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Apologetics of Human Freedom</title>
      <link>https://pritamchandra.github.io/post/2024/12/14/apologetics-of-human-freedom/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pritamchandra.github.io/post/2024/12/14/apologetics-of-human-freedom/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Underneath all conversations around theism against atheism lies still the problem of evil. Be it philosophers or laymen, from early centuries to contemporary ones, people still reject God primarily because they cannot reconcile a benevolent, omnipotent creator with our collectively painful and terrible existence.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sometimes, the inherent and solitary demand is the following - one can accept suffering from a good God only if it is good. Along these lines, one demands suffering to serve the existence of something bright, and, the presence of suffering must be the necessary precondition for the fullest expression of that brightness.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Creation Narrative - Scripture vs Science</title>
      <link>https://pritamchandra.github.io/post/2023/11/13/the-creation-narrative-scripture-vs-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://pritamchandra.github.io/post/2023/11/13/the-creation-narrative-scripture-vs-science/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It is not a wise thing to do to test scripture to align with the scientific narrative of creation, especially in relation to the chronology of the creation of various entities. This is not because they contradict, but simply because Scripture has a metaphysical underpinning which science is unable to take into account.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For example, time as we know it is demarcated by the objects in the space (heavenly bodies) and forces of interactions between them. These themselves are created in the third day of the Genesis narrative. So, what day one represents is not our familiar physical time (which was only created in day three). Neither the order of the days represents the chronology of creation.&#xA;Rather, the creation narrative should be attempted to be seen, with fear and trembling, from God&amp;rsquo;s perspective, which is outside time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
